Lilly Library collection of press kits and other film media releases, 1975-1995 PN1997 .A1
Lilly Library
- Press kits and other film media releases, 1975-1995
  - Hairspray, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Half Moon Street (Box 8)
  - Hamlet, (1990); Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - The Hand that Rocks the Cradle (Box 8)
  - Hannah and Her Sisters, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Hanna's War, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Happily Ever After, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 8)
  - Hard Promises (Box 8)
  - Hard to Hold, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - The Hard Way, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Harlem Nights, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Harley Davidson and the Marlboro Man (Box 8)
  - Haunted Honeymoon, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Havana, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - He Said, She Said, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Head Office, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Hear My Song (Box 8)
  - Hear No Evil (Box 8)
  - Heart, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Heart and Souls, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Heart Like a Wheel (Box 8)
  - Heartbreak Hotel, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Heartburn, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Heathers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Heaven Help Us, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - The Heavenly Kid, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Heavyweights, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Hellbound: Hellraiser II (Box 8)
  - Hello Again, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Hellraiser, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Hero (Box 8)
  - Hexed (Box 8)
  - The Hidden, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Hidden Agenda (Box 8)
  - Hiding Out, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - High Spirits, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Higher Learning Highlander 2: The Quickening (Box 8)
  - The Hitcher, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Hocus Pocus, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Hoffa Holy Matrimony, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Home Alone, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 8)
  - Home Alone 2 (Box 8)
  - Homeward Bound: The Incredible Journey, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Honey, I Blew Up the Kid Honey, I Shrunk the Kids, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Honeymoon Academy, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - Hoosiers (Box 8)
  - Hot Shots! Hot Shots! Part Deux The Hot Spot Hotel Colonial, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - House, (1986); Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - House II: The Second Story, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - House of Cards, (1993) (Box 8)
  - Houseguest Housesitter, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 8)
  - How I Got Into College (Box 9)
  - Hudson Hawk, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - The Hunted, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Husbands and Wives (Box 9)
  - I Love Trouble (Box 9)
  - I Love You to Death, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - I.Q. (Box 9)
  - I'll Do Anything (Box 9)
  - Immediate Family, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Immortal Beloved (Box 9)
  - In the Army Now, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - In the Line of Fire (Box 9)
  - In the Name of the Father, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 9)
  - Indian Summer (Box 9)
  - Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - The Inkwell (Box 9)
  - The Inner Circle (Box 9)
  - An Innocent Man (Box 9)
  - Internal Affairs, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Invaders from Mars, Includes slides (Box 9)
  - Invasion U.S.A., Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Iron Eagle (Box 9)
  - Iron Eagle II, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Iron Will, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Ironweed, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Ishtar (Box 9)
  - JFK, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jack the Bear (Box 9)
  - Jacob's Ladder, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jagged Edge, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - The January Man (Box 9)
  - Jason Goes to Hell: The Final Friday, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jaws: The Revenge, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jefferson in Paris, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jennifer 8 (Box 9)
  - The Jerky Boys, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jesus Was His Name, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jetsons: The Movie, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jewel of the Nile, Includes slides (Box 9)
  - Jo Jo Dancer, Your Life is Calling, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Johnny Be Good, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Johnny Dangerously, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Johnny Handsome, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - The Journey of Natty Gann, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - The Joy Luck Club, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Joy of Sex (Box 9)
  - Judge Dredd, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Judgment Night, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Juice, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jumpin' Jack Flash, Includes slides (Box 9)
  - The Jungle Book (Theatrical Re-Release), (1967); Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Jungle Fever, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photographs damaged) (Box 9)
  - Junior, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Just One of the Guys, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Just the Way You Are (Box 9)
  - K-9, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Kafka, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - Kansas, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - The Karate Kid Part II, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - The Karate Kid Part III, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - The Keep (Box 9)
  - Kindergarten Cop, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - King David, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 9)
  - King Kong Lives (Box 9)
  - King Ralph, Includes photographs or glossy prints. Includes Elizabeth II coronation-style memorabilia: plate, stamps, coin. (Box 9)
  - A Kiss Before Dying (Box 10)
  - Kiss of Death (Box 10)
  - Knight Moves (Box 10)
  - Krush Groove, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Kuffs, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - L.A. Story, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - La Bamba, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Labyrinth, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Lady and the Tramp (Theatrical Re-Release), Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Ladybugs (Box 10)
  - The Lair of the White Worm (Box 10)
  - The Land Before Time (Box 10)
  - Lassie (Box 10)
  - Last Action Hero (Box 10)
  - The Last Dragon, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - The Last Emperor, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - The Last of the Finest, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - The Last of the Mohicans (Box 10)
  - The Last Starfighters, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - The Lawnmower Man (Box 10)
  - A League of Their Own (Box 10)
  - Leaving Normal (Box 10)
  - Legal Eagles (Box 10)
  - The Legend of Billie Jean (Box 10)
  - The Lemon Sisters (Box 10)
  - Leonard Part 6, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Less Than Zero (Box 10)
  - Let It Ride, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Lethal Weapon (Box 10)
  - License to Drive (Box 10)
  - License to Kill (Box 10)
  - Life Stinks (Box 10)
  - Life with Mikey, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Lifeforce, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Light of Day, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Lightning Jack, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Like Father Like Son, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - The Lion King, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Lionheart, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Little Man Tate, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photographs damaged) (Box 10)
  - The Little Mermaid, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - The Little Rascals, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Little Women, (1994) (Box 10)
  - Listen to Me (Box 10)
  - Lock Up, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - The Longshot, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Look Who's Talking, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Look Who's Talking Now (Box 10)
  - Look Who's Talking Too, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photographs damaged) (Box 10)
  - Loose Cannons, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Lorenzo's Oil (Box 10)
  - Losing Isiah (Box 10)
  - Lost Angels, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Lost in Yonkers (Box 10)
  - Love at Large (Box 10)
  - Love Crimes (Box 10)
  - The Lover (Box 10)
  - Loverboy (Box 10)
  - A Low Down Dirty Shame, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 10)
  - Lucas, Includes slides (Box 10)
  - Mac and Me, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Mad Dog and Glory, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Mad Love, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Mad Max Beyond Thunderdome, Includes photographs or glossy prints (original folder water damaged, some photos stuck together) (Box 11)
  - Madame Souzatzka (Box 11)
  - Made in Heaven (Box 11)
  - Madhouse, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Major Payne, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Making Mr. Right, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Malone, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - The Man in the Moon, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Man of the House, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Man Trouble (Box 11)
  - The Man with One Red Shoe (Box 11)
  - The Manhattan Project, Includes slides (Box 11)
  - Manhunter, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Mannequin (Box 11)
  - Mannequin Two: On the Move (Box 11)
  - Marie: A True Story (Box 11)
  - Marked for Death (Box 11)
  - Married to the Mob, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - The Marrying Man (Box 11)
  - Masters of the Universe, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Matinee (Box 11)
  - Maxie, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Maximum Overdrive, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - The Mean Season, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Medicine Man (Box 11)
  - Melvin and Howard (Box 11)
  - Memories of Me (Box 11)
  - Men at Work, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Menace II Society (Box 11)
  - Mermaids, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - The Meteor Man (Box 11)
  - Miami Blues, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Miami Rhapsody, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Micki & Maude (Box 11)
  - Midnight Crossing (Box 11)
  - Midnight Run, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - The Mighty Ducks (Box 11)
  - Mighty Morphin Power Rangers: The Movie (Box 11)
  - The Mighty Quinn (Box 11)
  - The Milagro Beanfield War, Includes photographs or glossy prints (original folder torn) (Box 11)
  - Milk Money, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Millennium (Box 11)
  - Miller's Crossing (Box 11)
  - Million Dollar Mystery, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Miracle on 34th Street, (1994) (Box 11)
  - Mischief, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 11)
  - Missing in Action, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Braddock: Missing in Action III, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Mississippi Burning, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Mo' Better Blues, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Mo' Money (Box 11)
  - Mobsters, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photographs damaged) (Box 11)
  - Modern Love, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Money for Nothing, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - The Money Pit (Box 11)
  - Monkey Shines: An Experiment in Fear, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - The Monster Squad, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Moon Over Parador, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Moonstruck (Box 11)
  - The Morning After (Box 11)
  - Mortal Thoughts, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 11)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Bridge, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Mr. Baseball (Box 12)
  - Mr. Destiny, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Mr. Frost (Box 12)
  - Mr. Jones (Box 12)
  - Mr. Mom (Box 12)
  - Mrs. Doubtfire (Box 12)
  - Mrs. Soffel (Box 12)
  - The Muppet Christmas Carol, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Murphy's Law, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Murphy's Romance, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Music Box, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - My Boyfriend's Back, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - My Cousin Vinny (Box 12)
  - My Father, the Hero (Box 12)
  - My Girl, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - My Girl 2 (Box 12)
  - My Left Foot, Includes slides (Box 12)
  - My Life (Box 12)
  - My Life as a Dog (Box 12)
  - My Little Pony - The Movie, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - My Stepmother Is an Alien, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Mystery Date, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Nadine, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - The Naked Cage, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - The Naked Gun 2 ½: The Smell of Fear, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Naked Gun 33 1/3: The Final Insult, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Naked Lunch (Box 12)
  - The Name of the Rose, Includes slides (Box 12)
  - Narrow Margin, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Navy Seals, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Nell (Box 12)
  - Never Cry Wolf, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - New Adventures of Pippi Longstocking, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - A New Life, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Newsies (Box 12)
  - Next Karate Kid (Box 12)
  - Night and the City (Box 12)
  - Night Game (Box 12)
  - A Night in the Life of Jimmy Reardon (Box 12)
  - Night of the Living Dead, (1990) (Box 12)
  - Nightbreed (Box 12)
  - Nightflyers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Nightmare Before Christmas, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - A Nightmare on Elm Street 4: The Dream Master, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - 9 1/2 Weeks (Box 12)
  - No Escape, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - No Man's Land, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - No Mercy, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - No Small Affair, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - No Way Out, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Nobody's Fool, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - North Shore, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Not Without My Daughter (Box 12)
  - Nothing in Common, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Nuns on the Run (Box 12)
  - Of Mice and Men, (1992) (Box 12)
  - Off Beat, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Off Limits (Box 12)
  - Old Gringo, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Oliver & Company (Box 12)
  - Once Around, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Once Bitten, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Once Upon a Crime (Box 12)
  - Once Upon a Forest (Box 12)
  - One Crazy Summer, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - One Good Cop, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - One Magic Christmas (Box 12)
  - Only the Lonely (Box 12)
  - Opportunity Knocks, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Ordinary People, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 12)
  - Oscar (Box 12)
  - Out of Africa (Box 13)
  - Out of Bounds, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Outrageous Fortune, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - PCU (Box 13)
  - Pacific Heights (Box 13)
  - The Package, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - The Pagemaster (Box 13)
  - The Paper, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Paramedics (Box 13)
  - Parenthood, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Parents (Box 13)
  - A Passage to India, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Passed Away, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Patriot Games (Box 13)
  - The Pebble and the Penguin (Box 13)
  - Pee Wee's Big Adventure, Includes photographs or glossy prints (original folder water damaged) (Box 13)
  - Peggy Sue Got Married, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - The People Under the Stairs (Box 13)
  - Perfect, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Perfect Strangers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - The Perfect Weapon, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Permanent Record, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Pet Sematary, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Petal to the Metal (Box 13)
  - Peter Pan (Theatrical Re-Release), Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Phantasm II, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Philadelphia (Box 13)
  - Physical Evidence (Box 13)
  - The Pick-Up Artist (Box 13)
  - Pinocchio ( Theatrical Re-Release), 1984; Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Pinocchio and the Emperor of the Night (Box 13)
  - The Pistol – The Birth of a Legend (Box 13)
  - Planes, Trains and Automobiles (includes materials relating to Full House), Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Platoon (Box 13)
  - The Player (Box 13)
  - Poetic Justice (Box 13)
  - Point Break (Box 13)
  - Poltergeist II (Box 13)
  - Poltergeist III (Box 13)
  - Popeye, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Porky's, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Porky's Revenge, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 13)
  - Postcards from the Edge, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Prancer (Box 13)
  - A Prayer for the Dying (Box 13)
  - Predator, Includes slides (Box 13)
  - Predator 2 (Box 13)
  - Prelude to a Kiss (Box 13)
  - Pretty in Pink, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Pretty Woman (Box 13)
  - The Prince and the Pauper (Box 13)
  - Prince of Darkness (Box 13)
  - The Prince of Tides, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - The Princess Bride, Includes slides (Box 13)
  - The Principal, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Private Resort, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Prizzi's Honor, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Problem Child, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Problem Child 2, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photographs damaged) (Box 13)
  - The Professional (Box 13)
  - The Program (Box 13)
  - Project X, Includes slides (Box 13)
  - Promised Land (Box 13)
  - Punch Line, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Robert A. Heinlein's The Puppet Master, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 13)
  - Pure Luck, Includes photographs or glossy prints (photos discolored) (Box 13)
  - The Purple Rose of Cairo (Box 13)
  - Q & A, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Quicksilver, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Quigley Down Under, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Quiz Show, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Rad, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Radio Days, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Radio Flyer, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Radioland Murders, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - A Rage in Harlem (Box 14)
  - Rain Man, Includes photographs or glossy prints; Includes slides (Box 14)
  - Rainbow Brite and the Star Stealer, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Raising Arizona (Box 14)
  - Rambling Rose (Box 14)
  - Rambo: First Blood, Part II, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Rapid Fire (Box 14)
  - Raw, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Raw Deal, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Razor's Edge, (1984); Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - The Real McCoy, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Real Genius, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Reality Bites (Box 14)
  - Red Heat, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Red Sonja (Box 14)
  - Reds, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - The Ref (Box 14)
  - Regarding Henry, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Remains of the Day (Box 14)
  - Remo Williams: The Adventure Begins, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Renaissance Man, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Renegades, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - The Rescue, Includes photographs or glossy prints (front page of pamphlet torn) (Box 14)
  - Rescue Me, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - The Rescuers, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - The Rescuers Down Under (Box 14)
  - The Return of the Living Dead, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Return to Snowy River Part II: The Legend Continues (Box 14)
  - Return to the Blue Lagoon, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Revenge, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Revenge of the Nerds II: Nerds in Paradise (Box 14)
  - Reversal of Fortune, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Rich in Love (Box 14)
  - Rising Son (Box 14)
  - The River, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - A River Runs Through It (Box 14)
  - The River Wild, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Road House (Box 14)
  - The Road to Wellville (Box 14)
  - Rob Roy (Box 14)
  - Robin Hood: Men in Tights (Box 14)
  - RoboCop, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - RoboCop 2, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Rocky IV (Box 14)
  - Rocky V (includes poster) (Box 14)
  - The Rocky Horror Picture Show, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Romeo and Juliet (Box 14)
  - Romero (Box 14)
  - Rookie of the Year (Box 14)
  - Roommates, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Roots, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Roxanne, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Ruby (Box 14)
  - Rude Awakening, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Rudy (Box 14)
  - Rudyard Kipling's The Jungle Book, (1994); Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Run, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 14)
  - Runaway, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Runaway Train, Includes photographs or glossy prints (original folder water damaged) (Box 15)
  - The Running Man, Includes photographs or glossy prints (Box 15)
  - Running Scared (Box 15)
  - Rush (Box 15)